Guide to the Chelsea Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2004 Acquisition, 1937-2003; 4.8; (7 boxes)
  - Computer media and Audiovisual materials
    - Computer media, 82 3.5 inch disks, 3 Zip disks, 2 CDs
      - Colette's Pearls Trudy Lewis Word Perfect 3.1, 2004-genm-0923-d-0072; 1 (Box 22)
      - Sbarbaro poems G. Ridinger, 2004-genm-0923-d-0073; 1 (Box 22)
      - VALERIE ANN LEFF "MARLEY" FOR CHELSEA, 2004-genm-0923-d-0074; 1 (Box 22)
      - John TAYLOR - Apocalypse, 2004-genm-0923-d-0075; 1 (Box 22)
      - ROMULUS LINNEY HIS WIFE IN W.P.6.0, 2004-genm-0923-d-0076; 1 (Box 22)
      - CHELSEA 74 CONTENTS + CONTRIBUTORS CLARISWORK, 2004-genm-0923-d-0077; 1 (Box 22)
      - CHELSEA AT FORTY-FIVE by A. dePalchi, 2004-genm-0923-d-0078; 1 (Box 22)
      - BLAKE LYNCH, 2004-genm-0923-d-0079; 1 (Box 22)
      - Gemaio, 2003* Luigi - Seven poems FONTANELLA TRANS. by Emanuel di Pasquale, 2004-genm-0923-d-0080; 1 (Box 22)
      - Elisabeth Murawski Watershed, Zorba's, Long After Dark, Incas, I Lose, On Forgiving, 2004-genm-0923-d-0081; 1 (Box 22)
      - Ms. Lynne Lawner 245 E. 72nd St. Apt 20C New York, NY 10021-4522 TEXT ORELLI POEMS (ENG.) MICROSOFT WINDOWS 98, 2004-genm-0923-d-0082; 1 (Box 22)
      - Catherine Neuhardt Minor "Precursor" "Pressed Poppies" "Single Flower" "Crossed Bars" "Skirted Mirrors" also a copy of Biography, 2004-genm-0923-d-0083; 1 (Box 22)
      - T. Houghton: 3 poems for Chelsea 74 1. IBM word/Claris 2. Rich Text, 2004-genm-0923-d-0084; 1 (Box 22)
      - New England Financial Dec. 2001, 2004-genm-0923-d-0085; 1 (Box 22)
      - Jesse Lee Kerchoval 3 poems, 2004-genm-0923-d-0086; 1 (Box 22)
      - [no label information], 2004-genm-0923-d-0087; 1 (Box 22)
    - Audiovisual media
      - Galante, Carlo. Essenza carnale (setting of poems by Alfredo de Palchi for jazz ensemble and speaker), 2003; 1 CD (Box 23)
        Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Weidner, Lise. Creator of Living Poetry, undated; 1 CD (Box 23)
- April 2005 Acquisition, 1985-2002; 4.21; (5 boxes)
  - Chelsea Issues
    - Chelsea 72 (2002), 6 folders, including 1 CD (Box 24)
    - Chelsea 73 (2002), 3 folders, including 1 zip disk (Box 24)
    - Chelsea 74 (2003), 4 folders, including 2 CDs (Box 24)
    - Chelsea 75 (2003), 15 folders, including 2 3.5 inch disks, 2 zip disks, and 1 CD (Box 24)
    - Chelsea 75 (2003), 2 folders, including 17 3.5 inch disks and 2 CDs (Box 25)
    - Chelsea 76 (2004), 29 folders, including 6 3.5 inch disks and 5 CDs (Box 25)
    - Chelsea 76 (2004), 1 folder, including 2 CDs (Box 26)
    - Chelsea 76-77 (2004) (Box 26)
    - Chelsea 77 (2004), 27 folders, including 26 3.5 inch disks, 1 zip disk, and 6 CDs (Box 26)
  - Other Writings
    - Jackson, Laura (Riding). Essay read by Sona Raiziss (sound recording), 1985; 1 audiocassette
  - Computer media and audiovisual materials
    - Computer media, 51 3.5 inch disks, 4 zip disks, and 19 CDs
      Scope and Contents
      Disks 1-72, 74-75; number 73 not assigned.
      - 166393 SBI Disk, 2005-genm-0411-do-0001; 1 (Box 27)
      - CHELSEA REVISE 8-25-03, 2005-genm-0411-do-0002; 1 (Box 27)
      - Aug 12 REC'D 159374, 2005-genm-0411-do-0003; 1 (Box 27)
      - Amy Bleser Drift Sunday Mozart, 2005-genm-0411-do-0027; 1 (Box 27)
      - ELIZABETH McBRIDE INCLUSIONS by EMcBride Rich Text INCLUSIONS by EMcBride Word doc., 2005-genm-0411-do-0031; 1 (Box 27)
      - [no label information], 2005-genm-0411-do-0032; 1 (Box 27)
      - [no label information], 2005-genm-0411-do-0033; 1 (Box 27)
      - Elizabeth McBride, 2005-genm-0411-do-0034; 1 (Box 27)
      - Richard Kostelanetz, 2005-genm-0411-do-0035; 1 (Box 27)
      - For Chelsea Sarah Rees POEMS, 2005-genm-0411-do-0036; 1 (Box 27)
      - Alfredo - BACKUP, 2005-genm-0411-do-0037; 1 (Box 27)
      - CHELSEA MAGAZINE, 2005-genm-0411-do-0040; 1 (Box 27)
      - MARGO BERDESHEVSKY Chelsea Award 2004, 2005-genm-0411-do-0058; 1 (Box 27)
      - 576990 Chelsea/Nicole Johnson 2004, 2005-genm-0411-do-0059; 1 (Box 27)
      - Gerard Malanga 7 Poems, 2005-genm-0411-do-0065; 1 (Box 27)
      - Poems + Bio Chelsea Elena K Byrne, 2005-genm-0411-do-0066; 1 (Box 27)
      - Vivian Lawry Pig Sticker saved in RTF (MAC) and Microsoft Word Mac 98, 2001, 2005-genm-0411-do-0067; 1 (Box 27)
      - MONSON for Chelsea, 2005-genm-0411-do-0068; 1 (Box 27)
      - [no label information], 2005-genm-0411-do-0069; 1 (Box 27)
      - Sbi comp 176567 Chelsea 76 text + cover, 2005-genm-0411-do-0070; 1 (Box 27)
      - 8/2003 179877 Licht tunnel -Light tunnel- c. Nils -R.Schultze mils@schultze-krause.de, 2005-genm-0411-do-0071; 1 (Box 27)
      - SM-3366 179871, 2005-genm-0411-do-0072; 1 (Box 27)
      - CHELSEA 75 4-21-04, 2005-genm-0411-do-0074; 1 (Box 27)
      - 164007 Chelsea 73 Revise 3-19-03 RECEIVED MAR 20 2003, 2005-genm-0411-do-0075; 1 (Box 27)
      - Contents (Chelsea 75) Caproni / Condini Last part of contents and posthumous poems, 2005-genm-0411-do-0004; 1 (Box 27)
      - Ekiss - Chelsea Poems, 2005-genm-0411-do-0005; 1 (Box 27)
      - Four Mickeys Smoking c. 2003 Peggy Newland peggynewland@yahoo.com, 2005-genm-0411-do-0006; 1 (Box 27)
      - Rice, 2005-genm-0411-do-0007; 1 (Box 27)
      - Chelsea 75 Contributors, 2005-genm-0411-do-0008; 1 (Box 27)
      - June 2003 Josh Goldfaden's Story "The king of the ferns" saved 3 ways: Rich Text Format Word Document Word 5.1 for Macintosh, 2005-genm-0411-do-0009; 1 (Box 27)
      - Chelsea - 4 poems Nancy Naomi Carlson, 2005-genm-0411-do-0010; 1 (Box 27)
      - Jesse Upton: 1. Lover's Leap 2. Biographical Note, 2005-genm-0411-do-0011; 1 (Box 27)
      - Christiana L Langenberg "The Mean Distance from the Sun" Chelsea Award, 2005-genm-0411-do-0012; 1 (Box 27)
      - "Hunting Day" by Andy Gaudreau 503-737-0707 (For Dec. '03 issue), 2005-genm-0411-do-0013; 1 (Box 27)
      - Flesh in Glory! "Chelsea" 75 Victor Segalen notes authors Blake Robinson Wash OC, 2005-genm-0411-do-0014; 1 (Box 27)
      - PS (POSTSCRI) RTF WPS RENARDIE THOUZON VANGOGH RTF=RICH TEXT FORMAT WPS=WORKS WORD PROCESSOR --WINDOWS XP--, 2005-genm-0411-do-0015; 1 (Box 27)
      - Ventana Pilgrimage After Daphne Radha Marcum 4771 White Rock Circle, #E Boulder, CO 80301, 2005-genm-0411-do-0016; 1 (Box 27)
      - THE SONIA RAIZISS MEMORIAL FUND, 2005-genm-0411-do-0017; 1 (Box 27)
      - "TRANSVESTITE" KEYWORTH POEM 5-11-03, 2005-genm-0411-do-0018; 1 (Box 27)
      - 3 short short stories Gayle Rudinger x Chelsea 75, 2005-genm-0411-do-0019; 1 (Box 27)
      - Someone from Away By John J. McCann, 2005-genm-0411-do-0020; 1 (Box 27)
      - At This My Mid-Century… Susan L. Feldman 586 17th Avenue San Francisco, CA 94121, 2005-genm-0411-do-0021; 1 (Box 27)
      - Reviews - Chelsea 75, 2005-genm-0411-do-0022; 1 (Box 27)
      - L-SUTTON POEMS, 2005-genm-0411-do-0023; 1 (Box 27)
      - Kiley Moran Angular Velocity Cannibals etc., 2005-genm-0411-do-0024; 1 (Box 27)
      - MARK IRWIN Wordperfect 3.0 BRIEF HISTORY ICON TRANSLATION INSTRUCTIONS Wordperfect 3.0 ->3.5.1 then convert to Word 97/98 version, 2005-genm-0411-do-0025; 1 (Box 27)
      - MAC Word Daniela Gioseffi 57 Montague St. #8G Brooklyn Hts. New York, NY 11201-3356 A Conversation with Ishmael Reed + Bio by Daniela Gioseffi CHELSEA -75-Dec'03, 2005-genm-0411-do-0026; 1 (Box 27)
      - Lynn Parrish Sutton Mac Disk (802) 864-3740 lmpsutton@aol.com 3 poems Coyote The Secret Life of Stones Bullets and Shot Gun Shells for Chelsea-75, 2005-genm-0411-do-0028; 1 (Box 27)
      - Honor Hunter by JANSET BERKOK SHAMI, 2005-genm-0411-do-0029; 1 (Box 27)
      - Oliver Rice Brother WP25000, 2005-genm-0411-do-0030; 1 (Box 27)
      - Chelsea Logo + files, 2005-genm-0411-do-0038; 1 (Box 27)
      - NED CONDINI 8 Meadow lane Montvale, NJ 07645 USA Antologia o Mericolia, 2005-genm-0411-do-0039; 1 (Box 27)
      - MIA LEONIN, 2005-genm-0411-do-0041; 1 (Box 27)
      - Minietta "In No Particular Order: Menopause, Mid-life, and Motherhood", 2005-genm-0411-do-0042; 1 (Box 27)
      - Mac formatted "Conveniences" Claudette Bass, 2005-genm-0411-do-0043; 1 (Box 27)
      - ROGERS CAMELLIA_HALL.RTF, 2005-genm-0411-do-0044; 1 (Box 27)
      - Erik Raschke "The Day Ann Landers Died", 2005-genm-0411-do-0045; 1 (Box 27)
      - Malcolm Farley 4 Rooms for June 04 issue of "Chelsea", 2005-genm-0411-do-0046; 1 (Box 27)
      - TAYLOR reviews of Bertoldo Quignard bio, 2005-genm-0411-do-0047; 1 (Box 27)
      - Spitzer/Rimbaud review--TAYLOR Word 5, 2005-genm-0411-do-0048; 1 (Box 27)
      - Erba review -- John Taylor + bio Word 5, 2005-genm-0411-do-0049; 1 (Box 27)
      - Michelle Auerbach Catullus Translations Thanks, 2005-genm-0411-do-0050; 1 (Box 27)
      - Emanuel diPasquale's TRANSLATIONS of: 1. Attolico 2. Moroni, 2005-genm-0411-do-0051; 1 (Box 27)
      - 6 Luis Cernuda PROSE POEMS translated by Stephen Kessler in .RTF format 12/01/03, 2005-genm-0411-do-0052; 1 (Box 27)
      - JAMES HOEGARD trans. of O.Hahn: RTF Cello The Body Asks the Soul Looking Through the Window, 2005-genm-0411-do-0053; 1 (Box 27)
      - FIVE POEMS BY Guy GOFFETTE TRANSLATED BY MARILYN HACKER, 2005-genm-0411-do-0054; 1 (Box 27)
      - 4 POEMS JILLIAN WEISE, 2005-genm-0411-do-0055; 1 (Box 27)
      - Michael Palmer, 2005-genm-0411-do-0056; 1 (Box 27)
      - "Cleopatra's Needle" RTF for Chelsea 76 by Julia Ridley Smith, 2005-genm-0411-do-0057; 1 (Box 27)
      - Derek Nikitas "Hungry" Hungry.doc, 2005-genm-0411-do-0060; 1 (Box 27)
      - Chris Crittenden Cape Cod Canal rtf Xanadu Old Orchard Beach Levis Sage Coach Trail 207-733-2101 Ccrittenden@maine.edu 162 N. Lubec Rd Lubec, ME 04652, 2005-genm-0411-do-0061; 1 (Box 27)
      - The Somersault by Alexander Penn (Vladislav Todorov), 2005-genm-0411-do-0062; 1 (Box 27)
      - Michelle Detorie 1100 Robert E. Lee #5 Austin, TX 78704 (512) 448-1833 mdetorie@yahoo.com, 2005-genm-0411-do-0063; 1 (Box 27)
      - CONTRIBUTORS CHELSEA 76, 2005-genm-0411-do-0064; 1 (Box 27)
    - Audiovisual media
      - Jackson, Laura (Riding). Essay read by Sona Raiziss, 1985; 1 audiocassette (Box 28)
- November 2005 Acquisition, 1996-2005; 3.88; (6 boxes)
  - Chelsea Issues
    - Chelsea 72 (2002), 4 (Box 29)
    - Chelsea 73 (2003) (Box 29)
    - Chelsea 74 (2003) (Box 29)
    - Chelsea 75 (2003), 3 (Box 29)
    - Chelsea 76 (2004), 3 (Box 29)
    - Chelsea 77 (2004), 6 (Box 29)
    - Chelsea 78 (2005), 7 folders, including 1 CD (Box 29)
    - Chelsea 78 (2005), 19 folders, including 20 3.5 inch disks and 4 CDs (Box 30)
  - Chelsea Editions Publications
    - Caproni, Giorgio. The Earth's Wall: Selected Poems 1932-1986 (translated by Ned Condini), 2003-2004; 9 folders, including 1 CD (Box 30)
    - De Angelis, Milo. Between the Blast Furnaces and the Dizziness: A Selection of Poems, 1970-1999 (translated by Emanuel di Pasquale), 2002; 7 folders, including 3 3.5 inch disks (Box 31)
    - Sbarbaro, Camillo. Shavings: Selected Prose Poems, 1914-1940 (translated by Gayle Ridinger), 2005, undated; 2 folders, including 1 CD (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Taylor, John. The Apocalypse Tapestries, 2004-2005; 2 folders, including 3 3.5 inch disks (Box 31)
  - Other Writings
    - de Palchi, Alfredo. Anonymous Constellations (translated by Sona Raiziss). Drafts, 1996-2003, undated; 3 (Box 31)
    - de Palchi, Alfredo, Paradigma: tutte le poesie, 1947-2005 (proofs) (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Literary Prizes
    - Raiziss/de Palchi Translation Awards (applications), 2004; 2 (Box 31)
  - Computer media
    - PROCESSING SYSTEMS SoftMaster TM UPC Bar Code Image File(s) PostScript "EPS" Format File Format: MAC Disk Format: MAC PIPS REF: DM-6220 "First in Publication Bar Coding", 2005-genm-1117-l-0001; 1 (Box 33)
    - WHERE WE HAD ALREADY BEEN Milo de Angelis TRANS. by Emanuel di Pasquale PART I Michael Soft Word PC About 150 pp. overall, 2005-genm-1117-l-0002; 1 (Box 33)
    - Where we HAD Already Been Milo de Angelis Trans. by Emanuel di Pasquale PART II PC about 150 pp. overall, 2005-genm-1117-l-0003; 1 (Box 33)
    - Apocalypse - MANUSCRIPT Cover Comments - Back Cover Bio - Back Cover Title Pages TAYLOR, 2005-genm-1117-l-0004; 1 (Box 33)
    - Xenos logo blurbs, 2005-genm-1117-l-0005; 1 (Box 33)
    - PUBLICATION IDENTIFICATION + PROCESSING SYSTEMS SoftMaster TM UPC Bar Code Image File(s) PostScript "EPS" Format File Format: MAC Disk Format: MAC PIPS REF: DM-1689 "First in Publication Bar Coding", 2005-genm-1117-l-0006; 1 (Box 33)
    - sbi comp Chelsea 78 text, 2005-genm-1117-l-0007; 1 (Box 33)
    - Chelsea #78 SBI# 182951 cover files, 2005-genm-1117-l-0008; 1 (Box 33)
    - [no label information], 2005-genm-1117-l-0009; 1 (Box 33)
    - Natalka Bilotserkivets translations (O. Jennings), 2005-genm-1117-l-0010; 1 (Box 33)
    - Jonathan Liebson "A Courtship" [RTF format] Chelsea #78 ph#: 212 414-9423, 2005-genm-1117-l-0011; 1 (Box 33)
    - ALISTAIR ONG (along2000@hotmail.com) for CHELSEA MAGAZINE files: cardigan.rtf cardigan.doc ongbio.rtf (Cardigan, Towel, Glass Eye story), 2005-genm-1117-l-0012; 1 (Box 33)
    - MICHAEL PALMA ESSAY FOR CHELSEA 78, 2005-genm-1117-l-0013; 1 (Box 33)
    - temporary - along2000@hotmail.com ALISTAIR ONG, 2005-genm-1117-l-0014; 1 (Box 33)
    - Natalka Bilotserkivets translations O. Jennings, 2005-genm-1117-l-0015; 1 (Box 33)
    - GURCHARAN RAMPURI in WORD .doc + Rich Text format (from Judy Roy), 2005-genm-1117-l-0016; 1 (Box 33)
    - Cattafi/Ferrarelli Poems; bios, 2005-genm-1117-l-0017; 1 (Box 33)
    - Marie-Claire Boncquart "Paris Places-Chans" translated by Marilyn Hoche HACKER, 2005-genm-1117-l-0018; 1 (Box 33)
    - Mario Fratti Sincerity Mr Mario Fratti 145 W 55th St Apt 15D New York, NY 10019-5355, 2005-genm-1117-l-0019; 1 (Box 33)
    - Ryan Murphy (Morning, Stanzas, Four Port., Engine, Sandy, Untitled, 2005-genm-1117-l-0020; 1 (Box 33)
    - Michal Lando Poems, 2005-genm-1117-l-0021; 1 (Box 33)
    - Norman Minnick poems RTF, 2005-genm-1117-l-0022; 1 (Box 33)
    - Daniela GioSEFFi Mac MSWord doc. 3 poems + bio note CHELSEA Spring 2005, 2005-genm-1117-l-0023; 1 (Box 34)
      Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information
    - Patricia Lockwood, 2005-genm-1117-l-0024; 1 (Box 34)
    - Bridget Cross 7 poems., 2005-genm-1117-l-0025; 1 (Box 34)
    - Ted Matteys -The Hole in the Fog -Contributor's Note (rtf files), 2005-genm-1117-l-0026; 1 (Box 34)
    - Ryan Flaherty - - Chelsea, 2005-genm-1117-l-0027; 1 (Box 34)
    - Final copies, poems for Chelsea saved in Rich Text format Laura Esckelson, 2005-genm-1117-l-0028; 1 (Box 34)
    - Herberto Helder poems translated by Alexis Levitin for Chelsea (Feb. 2, '05), 2005-genm-1117-l-0029; 1 (Box 34)
    - VICTORIA BROCKMEIER, 2005-genm-1117-l-0030; 1 (Box 34)
    - CHELSEA EDITIONS SBARBARO, 2005-genm-1117-l-0031; 1 (Box 34)
    - DM-9401, 2005-genm-1117-l-0032; 1 (Box 34)
    - homomac, 2005-genm-1117-l-0033; 1 (Box 34)
- April 2006 Acquisition, 2004-2006; 2.5; (5 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Unsorted, 2005-2006, undated; 9 (Box 35)
  - Chelsea Issues
    - Chelsea 78 (2005), 1 CD
    - Chelsea 79 (2005), 10 folders, including 1 3.5 inch disk and 3 CDs (Box 35)
    - Chelsea 79 (2005), 4 folders, including 22 3.5 inch disks and 11 CDs (Box 36)
  - Chelsea Editions Publications
    - Sereni, Vittorio. Poesia, 2004-2006, undated; 7 (Box 36)
    - Cattafi, Bartolo. Winter Fragments: Selected Poems, 1945-1979 (translated by Rina Ferrarelli), 2005-2006; 3 (Box 37 (Oversize))
    - Fontanella, Luigi. Land of Time: Selected Poems, 1972-2003 (edited by Irene Marchegiani), 2006 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Computer Media
    - CHELSEA 79 COVER, 2006-genm-0414-b-0001; 1 (Box 38)
    - SM-7127, 2006-genm-0414-b-0002; 1 (Box 38)
    - Chelsea 79 Back Cover, 2006-genm-0414-b-0003; 1 (Box 38)
    - [no label information], 2006-genm-0414-b-0004; 1 (Box 38)
    - Frank Finale - 2 poems "On the Wing" and "The Vision", 2006-genm-0414-b-0005; 1 (Box 38)
    - F. Field -Malvern -Fallout, 2006-genm-0414-b-0006; 1 (Box 38)
    - RANDALL WATSON "song" "spirit" Biographical note, 2006-genm-0414-b-0007; 1 (Box 38)
    - DM-3176, 2006-genm-0414-b-0008; 1 (Box 38)
    - 2 TW Poems for Chelsea, 2006-genm-0414-b-0009; 1 (Box 38)
    - Ruby Rahman poems for Chelsea; bio dala for poets/translators for contributors notes from Carolyne Wright, 2006-genm-0414-b-0010; 1 (Box 38)
    - BOOK REVIEWS, 2006-genm-0414-b-0011; 1 (Box 38)
    - Chelsea Victor Rodríguez Núñez "Countersign" "Certainties" Translated by Katherine M. Hedeen, 2006-genm-0414-b-0012; 1 (Box 38)
    - Nadine Meyer bio. "For Those Floating Above Vitebsk", 2006-genm-0414-b-0013; 1 (Box 38)
    - Annabelle Yeeseul Yoo eau_de_vie@professionalexpert_com ph: (917) 714-1565 1)Throne on the Sea 2)The Castrato's Dream Life., 2006-genm-0414-b-0014; 1 (Box 38)
    - FOR CHELSEA 79 LADY WEDDING ANNIVERSARY IN ITALY CONTRIBUTOR'S NOTE BY SANDER ZULAUF, 2006-genm-0414-b-0015; 1 (Box 38)
    - Why Translate Dante, 2006-genm-0414-b-0016; 1 (Box 38)
    - Jenny Benjamin-Smith, 2006-genm-0414-b-0017; 1 (Box 38)
    - For Chelsea 79 "First Frost" "Mid-March at the Park, 2003" Contributor's Note -Donald Platt, 2006-genm-0414-b-0018; 1 (Box 38)
    - Voices Conversation by Brian Satrom, 2006-genm-0414-b-0019; 1 (Box 38)
    - Houghton Rich Text "Mother Cartoon" "Birthday Party" for CHELSEA 79, 2006-genm-0414-b-0020; 1 (Box 38)
    - Sleeping Baby -Glori Simmons, 2006-genm-0414-b-0021; 1 (Box 38)
    - Sonia Raiziss 9 poems after the piece our necessity, 2006-genm-0414-b-0022; 1 (Box 38)
    - Chelsea 79 Contents Notes on contributors, 2006-genm-0414-b-0023; 1 (Box 39)
    - Patrick Hicks, 2006-genm-0414-b-0024; 1 (Box 39)
    - Terry Caesar Cellphones 2 in 1. Word 2. Rich Text Terry Caesar, 2006-genm-0414-b-0025; 1 (Box 39)
    - Stuart Greenhouse poems "Cowrie Apostrophe" and "Too" For Chelsea, Issue 79, 2006-genm-0414-b-0026; 1 (Box 39)
    - NOEL CONNEELY 2 POEMS 1). SCATTER 2). FIVECENTS, 2006-genm-0414-b-0027; 1 (Box 39)
    - "Ponte Vedra" "The kidnapping" by Daniel Mark Epstein, 2006-genm-0414-b-0028; 1 (Box 39)
    - F. FIELD - POETRY MALVERN, ACK. FALLOUT, 2006-genm-0414-b-0029; 1 (Box 39)
    - Robert Funge PO Box 1225 San Carlos, CA 94070 (650) 592 7720 'Dear Friend, (I'm full of good news)' 'Dear Friend, (You mail the envelope)' 'Dear Friend, (Awhile ago I wrote)', 2006-genm-0414-b-0030; 1 (Box 39)
    - RAYMOND LUCZAK - POEMS for CHELSEA 79 4.29.05, 2006-genm-0414-b-0031; 1 (Box 39)
    - Frank Finale - 2 poems "On the Wing" and "The Vision", 2006-genm-0414-b-0032; 1 (Box 39)
    - Alfred Clemente, "Afraid of the Dark" (in Rich Text Format) 4.27.05, 2006-genm-0414-b-0033; 1 (Box 39)
    - HISTORICAL OPPITY by ROMULUS LINNEY IN Word Perfect 6.0 callup: "EVANGELI", 2006-genm-0414-b-0034; 1 (Box 39)
    - Friedmann for Chelsea 79, 2006-genm-0414-b-0035; 1 (Box 39)
    - [no label information], 2006-genm-0414-b-0036; 1 (Box 39)
    - [no label information], 2006-genm-0414-b-0037; 1 (Box 39)
    - Robert Bence 2 poems, 2006-genm-0414-b-0038; 1 (Box 39)
- August 2006 Acquisition, 1998-2006; 1.29; (3 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Unsorted, 2005-2006, undated; 7 folders, including 3 3.5 inch disks (Box 40)
  - Chelsea Issues
    - Chelsea 75 (2003) (Box 41 (Oversize))
    - Chelsea 76 (2004) (Box 41 (Oversize))
    - Chelsea 77 (2004) (Box 41 (Oversize))
    - Chelsea 80 (2006) (Box 41 (Oversize))
    - Chelsea 80 (2006), 5 (Box 40)
  - Chelsea Editions Publications
    - Capioli, Rosita. Wrath of the Roses, 2006, undated; 3 (Box 40)
    - Moroni, Mario. Icarus' Land: Selected Poems, 1989-2002, 2005, undated (Box 40)
  - Other Papers
    - Laura (Riding) Jackson (exhibit, Cornell University), 1998, undated (Box 40)
  - Computer media
    - Not Everything Updated excerpt, 2006-genm-723-0001; 1 (Box 42)
    - Not Everything Excerpt, 2006-genm-723-0002; 1 (Box 42)
    - "Not" Excerpt St Cloud, 2006-genm-723-0003; 1 (Box 42)
- June 2007 Acquisition, 2006-2007; 1.63; (3 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Unsorted, 2006-2007; 10 folders, including 1 CD (Box 43)
  - Chelsea Issues
    - Chelsea 81 (2006), 10 folders, including 5 3.5 inch disks and 28 CDs (Box 43)
  - Computer media
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0001; 1 (Box 44)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0002; 1 (Box 44)
    - Final Dickinson Essay by Daniela Gioseffi with all corrections for Typesetter Sept 2006 Chelsea 80, 2007-genm-8040-0003; 1 (Box 44)
    - Henry St. Cloud July 15, 2007-genm-8040-0004; 1 (Box 44)
    - Book Reviews 81, 2007-genm-8040-0005; 1 (Box 44)
    - whfc.doc, 2007-genm-8040-0006; 1 (Box 44)
    - For Chelsea Daniela Gioseffi c2006 Emily Dickinson Essay, 2007-genm-8040-0007; 1 (Box 44)
    - Taylor, 2007-genm-8040-0008; 1 (Box 44)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0009; 1 (Box 44)
    - Elegy with Fig Tree -Margaret Rabb, 2007-genm-8040-0010; 1 (Box 44)
    - Poems By William Delman, 2007-genm-8040-0011; 1 (Box 44)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0012; 1 (Box 44)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0013; 1 (Box 44)
    - John Kistner "The Child Knife" poem for Chelsea email: jkistner@earthlink.net, 2007-genm-8040-0014; 1 (Box 44)
    - E.L.R. POEMS, 2007-genm-8040-0015; 1 (Box 44)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0016; 1 (Box 44)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0017; 1 (Box 44)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0018; 1 (Box 44)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0019; 1 (Box 44)
    - Hightower Poem "Gattopardo", 2007-genm-8040-0020; 1 (Box 44)
    - Bodies at Rest; Bodies in Motion Lael Ewy, 2007-genm-8040-0021; 1 (Box 44)
    - MOOLTEN "PORTRAIT" POEM, 2007-genm-8040-0022; 1 (Box 44)
    - 4 poems by Ned Condini 111 Eagle Chase Lane Etowah, NH 28729 USA, 2007-genm-8040-0023; 1 (Box 44)
    - Timothy Houghton MS WORD Poems for Chelsea 81 "Bible Oil" and "Modestly Alive", 2007-genm-8040-0024; 1 (Box 45)
    - D. GRÜNZWEIG 5 POEMS TR. D. WYNAND, 2007-genm-8040-0025; 1 (Box 45)
    - Jul 18, '06 "Joseph and Miss…" 1. C-H Ramuz 2. C-H Ramux + Blake Robinson, 2007-genm-8040-0026; 1 (Box 45)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0027; 1 (Box 45)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0028; 1 (Box 45)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0029; 1 (Box 45)
    - Stephen Kessler translations of 2 poems by Cernuda, 2007-genm-8040-0030; 1 (Box 45)
    - Rimbaud trans by Louis Bourgeois, 2007-genm-8040-0031; 1 (Box 45)
    - from Tre Stazioni, Anedda, 2007-genm-8040-0032; 1 (Box 45)
    - Emily Dickinson "Lover of science" by Daniela Gioseffi ©2006 Chelsea #81 Dec., 2007-genm-8040-0033; 1 (Box 45)
    - [no label information], 2007-genm-8040-0034; 1 (Box 45)
- November 2007 Acquisition, 1985-2007; 4.04; (8 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Academy of American Poets, 2004, undated (Box 46)
    - Academy of American Poets (Box 48 (Oversize))
    - Unsorted, 2007 (Box 48 (Oversize))
    - Unsorted, 2007-2008, undated; 8 (Box 46)
  - Chelsea Issues
    - Chelsea 82/83 (2007), 18 (Box 46)
    - Chelsea 82/83 (2007), 3 folders, including 2 3.5 inch disks and 33 CDs (Box 47)
      Includes submissions by Gerard Malanga.
  - Other Writings
    - Cattafi, Ada (prints of paintings), 2007 (Box 47)
    - de Palchi, Afredo. Paradigma: tutte le poesie, 1947-2005 (reviews), undated (Box 47)
    - Jackson, Laura (Riding). Essay read by Sona Raiziss (sound recording), 1985; 1 audiocassette
  - Other Papers
    - Consorzio pro loco basso veronese (plaque), 1998 April 24 (Box 49 (Art))
    - Small Press Book Fair. Celebration of Literature Award (plaque), 1995 (Box 50)
    - Clippings, 2004 (Box 47)
    - Testa, Fulvio. Watercolors, undated (Box 47)
    - Xenos Books (t-shirts), undated; 2 T-Shirts (Box 51)
    - Printed material, 2007; 6 (Box 47)
    - Drawings and prints, undated (Box 48 (Oversize))
    - Manuscripts removed from books (Box 47)